翻译：业余渣翻人 微博：业余渣翻人 欢迎打赏支持
黄石前情提要...
Previously on Yellowstone...
从黄石河里捞出了一个无线电项圈
Fished a radio collar out of the Yellowstone River.
附近最近有看到狼吗？
Seen any wolves around lately?
听起来像偷猎者
Sounds like poachers.
确实  愿意跟我们走一趟吗？
Sure does.  Care to ride with us?
莫妮卡想举行一个葬礼
Monica wants to have a funeral.
她想葬在这里 这样她可以常来看看
She wants him here where she can visit.
无论她想要什么 你就给她吧 孩子
Whatever she wants, you- you give it, son.
我分身乏术
I can't serve both.
我选择她 也选择我的儿子
I choose her and I choose my son.
你答应过的 你拿了几百万的租赁费!
You promised and you took millions in lease payments!
你无话可辩了
You have no case.
你也知道这一点
And you know it.
你比我想象的要好
You're better than I expected.
我是来找软着陆点的
I am here just to find a soft landing.
你明天晚上有多忙？
How busy are you tomorrow night?
纽约方面希望撤销诉讼
New York would like to drop the suit.
想办法毁掉这个家庭 埃利斯
Find a way to ruin this family, Ellis.
嘿 我们去波兹曼的一个酒吧吧
Hey, let's go to a bar in Bozeman.
这是个坏主意 每次如此
Yeah, that's a bad idea every time.
你真是个高大威猛的可人 不是吗
Aren't you a tall drink of water?
我已经结婚了 去吧
I'm married. Go on.
我要带你丈夫回家
I'm taking your husband home.
今天是哪一天？
What day is it?
应该是星期四吧
Thursday, I think.
你怎么了？
What happened to you?
该死的男人
Fucking men.
把你干得很爽 是吧？
Worked you over pretty good, huh?
我说的是逮捕我的那个警察
I'm talking about the cop that arrested me.
这家伙一星期有三个晚上在俱乐部
Prick is in the club three nights a week.
他就不能让我休息一下吗？
He can't cut me a break?
他们以驾驶不当的罪名抓你？
They get you for D.U.I.?
严重的攻击行为
Aggravated assault.
一个来自加利福尼亚的婊子想和我丈夫上床
Some bitch from California tried to fuck my husband
所以 我用啤酒瓶打了她
so I beat her with a beer bottle.
所以 你就像他妈的一个罪犯
So, you're like a fucking criminal.
这只是被蔑视的女人的愤怒
I am the wrath of a woman scorned.
随你怎么说吧
Call it what you will.
总是一些来自加利福尼亚的婊子
It's always some bitch from California.
每次都是
Every fucking time.
贝瑟尼·达顿 我们走吧
Bethany Dutton. Let's go.
你看起来不像是叫贝瑟尼的
You don't look like a Bethany.
我不是贝瑟妮 我是贝丝
I'm not a Bethany. I'm a Beth.
我的英雄
My hero.
谈完后敲门
Knock when you're done.
孩子 你这次真的他妈的做了
Boy, you have really fucking done it this time.
有什么大不了的 杰米？
What's the big deal, Jamie?
我在波兹曼的一个酒吧打架了
I got into a bar fight in Bozeman.
我是说 蒙大拿州旅游委员会
I mean, Montana Board of Tourism
应该把这句话放在他妈的T恤上
should put that on fucking t-shirts.
我不认为蒙大拿州旅游委员会
I don't think the Montana Board of Tourism
会喜欢当地人殴打
is too fond of locals beating the shit
度假游客的行为
out of tourists on vacation.
好吧 这就是为什么我给你打电话
Well, that's why I called you.
你可以隐瞒下去的 不是吗？
You can find the rug to sweep this under, right?
这次可没有了 贝丝
There is no rug for this one, Beth.
这是县检察官的事情
It's a County Attorney issue.
所以 你最好的选择是祈祷这个女人有飞机要赶
So your best bet is to hope this woman has a plane to catch
或者她因宿醉而不能来这里
or she's too hungover to come down here
并提出正式指控
and file formal charges.
这就是你的法律建议？
This is your legal advice?
坐在这里祈祷？
Sit here and hope?
这不是建议 这是你唯一的选择
It's not advice. It's your only option.
如果她不提出指控的话
If she doesn't file charges
这个 "如果"机会渺茫  考虑到
and that's a big fucking "if" considering the photo
我看到的她鼻青脸肿的照片
I saw of the grapefruit on her forehead
那么 我将请求县检察官
then I will ask the County Attorney
看在你控制情绪能力下降的基础上
to show some mercy based on your diminished capacity
对你仁慈一点
to control your fucking emotions.
所以 是的 你就乖乖坐在这里祈祷吧
So, yeah, you just sit here and hope.
但无论如何 如果这事传到媒体上
But no matter what, if this reaches the press
这会让我们父亲非常难堪
it's a big embarrassment for our father.
你是说我的父亲
You mean my father.
你父亲已经没有机会出丑了 不是吗 杰米？
Your father's out of chances to be embarrassed, isn't he, Jamie?
我要回我的牢房去了
I'm going to go back to my cell.
我要去打个盹
I'm going to take a nap.
而你要坐在这个地方该死的台阶上
And you're going to sit on the fucking steps of this place
你要等着加州小姐走过来
and you're going to wait for Miss California
当她走过来时 你要阻止她
to walk up, and when she does, you are going to stop her.
我到底该怎么才能做到呢？
How the hell am I going to do that?
这不是我的问题 杰米
It's not my problem, Jamie.
嘿 达顿攻击案是你负责吗？
Hey. You got this Dutton assault case?
呃 是的 先生
Uh, yes, sir.
为什么没有对投诉人提出指控？
Why no charges against the complainant?
那是一场酒吧斗殴 不是吗？
It was a bar fight, wasn't it?
从报告上看 那是一场地狱般的酒吧斗殴
It was one hell of a bar fight from the report.
酒吧斗殴中没有自我防卫这一说法
There is no self defense in a bar fight
也就是说 受害者也可以是被告
which is to say the victim is a defendant as well.
她要来吗？
Is she coming in?
我现在在等她  我和你一起等
I'm waiting for her now.  I'll wait with you.
你和蒙大拿州教育家有午宴
You have the Montana Educators Luncheon at noon.
取消它
Cancel it.
州长 我认为这会传达出错误的信息
Governor, I think that sends the wrong message.
好吧 到底是谁会参加蒙大拿州教育家的午宴？
All right, who exactly attends the Montana Educators Luncheon?
所有人 佩里参议员也会去
Everyone. Senator Perry will be there.
议员们 学校校长们
Legislators, School Superintendents
蒙大拿州的州长
the President of Montana State.
如果没有教育工作者在场
Why do they call it the Educators Euncheon
他们为什么叫它 "教育者午宴"？
if there's no educators there?
今天是星期四 克拉拉 所有的教育工作者都在学校里
It's Thursday, Clara, all the educators are in school.
告诉你吧 当教育工作者午宴
Tell you what, when the Educators' Luncheon
是关于教师的 我就去
is about teachers, I'll go.
他们是谁？
Who are they?
那是政策顾问的会议
It's the policy advisors' meeting.
谁的政策顾问？
Policy advisors for who?
你的
For you.
我的政策顾问是如何能在没有我的情况下
How can my policy advisors have a meeting
举行政策商讨会议的？
about policies without me?
嗯...
Um...
你坐我位置上了
You're in my seat.
我们今天商讨的是什么政策？
So what policies are we discussing today?
没有人知道？
Nobody?
让我们看看...
Let's see...
"根据美国的绿色倡议
"In accordance with the U.S. Green initiative
"蒙大拿州正在将粉河县的7000英亩土地
"Montana is leasing 7,000 acres in Powder River County
租赁给太阳能源公司 "
to Sun Energies."
太阳能源公司是什么东西？
What is Sun Energies?
它是一家太阳能农场公司
It's a solar farm company.
嗯 那你是？
Mm. And you are?
斯坦利... 罗伯茨
Stanley... Roberts.
你的职位是？
And you are?
你的首席政策顾问 州长先生
Your chief policy advisor, Mr. Governor.
嗯 很高兴见到你
Well, nice to fucking meet you.
我想安排一次午餐 但你...
I tried to schedule a lunch but you're...
她说你不接受午餐
She said you aren't taking lunches.
你的办公室在哪里 斯坦利？
Where's your office, Stanley?
就在... 就在大厅里
Just... Right down the hall.
你知道吗？我的也是
Know what? So is mine.
你有没有想过要过来打个招呼？
Ever dawn on you just to come by and say howdy?
我错了
My mistake.
我想也是
I'd say.
让我们看看我还提出了哪些政策
Let's see what other policies I'm proposing.
暂停粉河县州土地上的天然气租赁
Suspend natural gas leases on state land
以支持
in Powder River County to support
"艾草松鸡恢复项目"
the Sage Grouse Restoration Project.
嗯 艾草松鸡的数量急剧下降
Um, there's been a precipitous drop in sage grouse numbers
而且 有经验数据表明
and there is empirical evidence
天然气勘探和开采
that gas exploration and extraction
对艾草松鸡的环境产生了负面影响
have a negative impact on the sage grouse environment.
你认为七千英亩的太阳能电池板
And what effect do you think seven thousand acres
会对艾草松鸡的环境产生什么影响？
of solar panels are going to have on their environment?
没有...没有证据表明太阳能电池板
There's... no evidence that solar panels
会对艾草松鸡的环境产生任何影响
would have any impact on the sage grouse environment.
当他们安装太阳能电池板时
What do they do with the sage brush
他们会是如何处理灌木丛的？
when they put in the solar panels?
他们 他们...
They, they...
他们会在装入太阳能电池板之前清除它
They would clear it before putting in the solar panels.
他们会清除灌木丛
They remove the sage brush.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
艾草松鸡是生活在灌木丛的
Sage grouse live in the sage brush.
确实
They do.
你不认为清除灌木丛
And you don't think removing the sage brush
会对其数量产生影响吗？
is going to have an effect on the population?
我只是说没有证据...
I just said there's no evidence--
知道你让我害怕的是什么吗 斯坦利？你是认真的
Know what scares me about you, Stanley? You're serious.
你看着我 告诉我你不是在开玩笑
You're looking at me and you're not joking.
我想今天我的议程中最重要的
I think tops on my agenda today
将是预算纪律 你们都被解雇了
is going to be budget discipline. You're all fired.
我非常注意我们纳税人的钱
I'm very mindful of our tax payers' money
而你们都在浪费它
and you are all wasting it.
政策相关的还是靠我自己吧 克拉拉
I'll advise myself on policy, Clara.
我们刚刚节省了多少钱？
How much money did we just save?
我想说...
I would say...
大概有160万美元的工资和福利金
Roughly 1.6 Million dollars in salary and benefits
如果你是认真的话
if you're serious.
噢 我非常认真
Oh, I'm pretty serious.
看吧
Look at that.
对蒙大拿州来说 这是多么美好的一天
What a great day for the State of Montana.
接下来去哪里？
Where to next?
我们有一个紧急会议 与公园官员
We have an emergency meeting with park officials
以及美国鱼类及野生动植物管理局
and U.S. Fish and Wildlife.
关于什么的紧急会议？
Emergency meeting about what?
没有说
Doesn't say.
通常意味着有人在公园里死亡
Usually means someone died in the park.
他们在你的办公室里
They're in your office.
有什么紧急情况？
What's the emergency?
州长 我们想让你看一下这张地图
Governor, we'd like for you to take a look at this map.
红线表示一个无线电领狼的路径
The red lines indicate the path of a radio-collared wolf
与救援溪的狼群有关
associated with the Rescue Creek pack.
好的
All right.
你可以看到...
As you can see...
无论我们在哪里看到这些集群
Wherever we see these clusters
我们就会联想到一个捕食现场
we associate with a kill site.
他们会在尸体上吃上几天 然后他们会继续前进
They'll feed on a carcass for a few days, then they'll move on.
它们大约在三周前离开公园
They left the park here roughly three weeks ago
他们沿着树线走到这里
they traveled the tree line to here
然后 它们从这个山谷里走下到这里
then they dropped down in this valley to here.
嗯哼
Mm hm.
那是我的牧场
That's my ranch.
我们知道
We're aware.
狼群在这里聚集了三天
The wolves clustered here for three days
围绕着什么 似乎是个捕食现场
around what appears to be a kill
然后他们直接向南移动了30英里到这里
then they move straight south for thirty miles to here.
现在 那是黄石河...
Now, that's the Yellowstone River...
根据数据 它们跳进河里
They jump into the river, according to this data
向下游游了五英里
and they swim downstream for five miles.
我不知道狼会在河里游泳
Wasn't aware wolves swam down rivers.
它们不会
They don't.
我们在河里找到了一个无线电项圈
We recovered one of the radio collars from the river.
你想说什么？
What are you getting at?
我们认为这些狼是在你的农场里被杀死的
We think the wolves were killed on your ranch
然后把项圈运回了公园
and the collars transported back to the park.
你们认为是我的牛仔们杀了那些狼
You think my cowboys killed those wolves.
我们认为是你的牛仔杀了那些狼
We think your cowboys killed those wolves.
是的 先生？
Yes sir?
有看到任何狼攻击我们的牛群吗？
We had any wolves messing with the cattle?
狼群？没有 先生
Wolves? No sir.
鱼类及野生动植物管理局也来问过同样的问题
Fish and Wildlife came by asking the same thing.
好的
All right.
你们也听到了
There you have it.
听着 如果它们袭击了你的牛群
Look, if they get into your cattle
你就得做你该做的事
you gotta do what you gotta do.
我的猜测是：他们从远处射杀他们
My guess: they shot them from a distance
没有注意到他们的项圈
didn't notice the collar
然后 被吓坏了 试图掩盖他们的踪迹
got spooked and tried to cover their tracks.
这些无线电项圈并不是由我们监控的
These radio collars aren't monitored by us.
一个非政府组织支付了这项研究的费用
An NGO pays for this research
他们拥有和我们一样的数据
and they have the same data we have
他们也会得出同样的结论
and they are going to draw the same conclusion.
当他们做出结论时
When they do
他们会全力以赴地来对付你 州长
they will come after you with both barrels, Governor.
我很期待
Look forward to it.
还有什么问题吗？
Anything else?
谢谢你们 先生们 州长 我们有...
Thank you, gentlemen. Governor, we have the--
是的
Yep.
环保组织可能真有点麻烦
Environmental groups can be a real problem.
可不是吗
Yeah, you don't say.
我是克拉拉
This is Clara.
我是杰米 让我跟他说话
It's Jamie, let me speak to him.
州检察长
Attorney general.
怎么了？
Yeah?
好吧 有很大可能我可以使这事情消失
All right, there is a good chance I can make this go away.
但是 万一我做不到 我需要你知道
But, in case I can't, I need you to know
我在波兹曼的警察局里
that I'm in police station in Bozeman
希望能说服一个年轻女人放弃
hoping to convince a young woman to drop
打算对你女儿
the aggravated assault charges she plans
严重攻击的指控
to file against your daughter.
该死的一天
This fucking day.
我可以 呃...
Can I, uh...
可以告诉我事情起因吗 杰米？
Can I have a little more context, Jamie?
她在酒吧里对贝丝大放厥词
Yeah, she mouthed off to Beth in a bar
事情进展就跟你预期那样
and it went about how you'd expect.
好吧 随时向我汇报情况 Just, uh, keep me posted.
All right. Just, uh, keep me posted.
我的团队里有没有危机管理人呢?
Is there a crisis manager on my team, by any chance?
那应该是你的新闻秘书 你从来没有雇用过
Well, that would be your press secretary who you never hired
所以 我猜你的危机管理人是我
so I guess your crisis manager is me.
能给我点时间吗？
Can I have a minute?
玩得开心吗？
Having fun yet?
你应该没可能想换工作吧？
No chance you'd want to change jobs?
你会更讨厌这份工作的
You'd hate this one more.
你有可能在海伦娜吗？
Any chance you're in Helena?
很有可能
A good chance.
有什么午餐计划？ 现在没有了
Lunch plans?  Not anymore.
你知道Benny's Bistro吗？ 当然
You know Benny's Bistro?  Sure.
中午？ 你让我的日子好过了
Noon?  You made my day.
是的 也许你也能让我的日子好过一点 一会儿见
Yeah, maybe you can make mine. See you in a bit.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
布鲁尔小姐
Miss Brewer.
我知道你想起诉
I understand you'd like to press.
非常想
Very much.
我觉得我必须指出的是 这样做
I feel I must point out that by doing so
你也会成为被告人
you are exposing yourself to prosecution.
为什么会这样？
How am I doing that?
酒吧斗殴不存在自我辩护的说法
There is no self defense claim in a bar fight.
我猜你当时喝了酒 而且我知道是你
I assume you had been drinking, and I understand you
接近达顿小姐并煽动了这一事件
approached Miss Dutton and instigated the incident.
我没有煽动任何事情
I didn't instigate anything.
哦 嗯...
Oh, um...
让我看看
Let me see.
你走近达顿小姐并说
Yeah, you approached Miss Dutton and stated
"我要带你丈夫回家
"I'm taking your husband home.
"你可以跟我们一起在旁边看
"You can come with us and watch
或者他可以明天告诉你 "
or he can tell you about it tomorrow."
这不是你说的话吗？
Are those not your words?
我的意思是...
I mean...
我是在开玩笑
I was kidding.
嗯
Mm.
她并不觉得这很有趣
She didn't find it very funny.
可不是吗
No shit.
作出威胁伤害他人的声明或行动
Making statements or actions that threaten harm to another
或者让他们觉得自己处于危险之中 就是攻击
or make them feel they are in danger is assault.
你不一定要打人才是攻击行为
You don't have to hit somebody to commit assault
你只需要提出一个威胁
you just have to present a threat.
你提出了威胁
You presented the threat.
因此 如果你提出指控
So if you press charges
州政府必须对你提出指控
the state must press charges against you.
由于你不是蒙大拿州的居民
And since you are not a resident of Montana
你有逃跑的可能 你的保释将被拒绝
you present a flight risk and you bail will be withheld.
你明白这意味着什么吗？
Do you understand what that means?
所以她就...
So she just...
她就这样逃脱了？
She just gets away with it?
她并没有逃脱什么
She didn't get away with anything.
她在监狱里过了一夜 她将被指控
She spent the night in jail and she's going to be charged
扰乱秩序的行为
with disorderly conduct.
选择是你的
The choice is yours.
我迫不及待地想离开这个州
I can't wait to get out of this state.
那些该死的乡巴佬
Those fucking hillbillies.
嗯 这种感觉是相互的
Well, the feeling is mutual.
我可以离开吗？
May I leave?
请吧
Please.
为我节省了大量的文书工作
Saved me a ton of paperwork.
谢谢
Thanks.
很高兴能帮上忙
Happy to help.
他们在做什么？
What're they doing?
我猜是为了凯西的儿子
For Kayce's boy is my guess.
他们告诉我们这个地方
They told us this spot.
如果我知道的话 我就会为你挖那个洞了
If I would've known I would have dug that hole for you.
我们不介意 这也是仪式的一部分
We don't mind. It's part of the ceremony.
那里有一匹死马
There's a dead horse over there.
他什么时候死的？
When did he die?
他星期一死的
He died Monday.
我有一个挖掘机明天要来埋葬他
I got an excavator coming out tomorrow to bury him.
我们现在就把他埋了
We'll bury him now.
我们会把他放在男孩旁边的土地上
We'll put him in the ground beside the boy.
我能问你为什么吗？
Can I ask you why?
你可以问 但我不打算回答
You can ask, but I ain't gonna answer.
凯西对这个没有意见吧？
Kayce's all right with this, then?
他知道
He knows.
好吧 你需要一个大洞
Well, you're gonna need a big hole.
杰克 伊森 跑回谷仓去
Jake, Ethan, run back to the barn
给我们拿一堆铲子来
and grab us a bunch of shovels.
我来帮你 莫
I'll help you, Mo.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不要希望得到你不想要的东西
Don't wish for what you don't want.
你现在已经在里面了 约翰 你不妨接受它
You're in it now, John. You might as well accept it.
好吧
All right.
向我解释一下这份工作 因为它毫无意义
Explain this job to me, because it makes no sense.
我所做的就是去中学和剪彩
All I do is go to middle schools and ribbon cuttings.
好吧 当立法机构在开会的时候
Well, when the legislature's in session
你会为剪彩祈祷的
you'll be praying for ribbon cuttings.
在一天结束的时候 蒙大拿州是一个企业
At the end of the day, Montana is a business
12,000名员工 600,000名客户
12,000 employees, 600,000 customers
而你是首席执行官 这就是全部
and you're the CEO, and that's all there is.
而你真的需要改变你的观点
And you really need to change your perspective
关于这些学校会议
about these school meetings, too.
你知道 这些孩子会记住与州长的会面
You know, these kids are gonna remember meeting the governor
在他们的余生中
for the rest of their lives.
谁知道呢 你甚至可能激励他们中的一个人
And who knows, you might even inspire one of them
有朝一日成为州长
to become the governor one day.
我的意思是 我就是这样被激励的
I mean, that's how I was inspired.
好吧 我明白了
All right, point taken.
看来我踩到了一些地雷
I stepped on a few land mines it appears.
已经踩了？
Already?
别人替我踩了
Others stepped on them for me.
我的女儿在酒吧打架了
Seems my daughter got herself into a bar fight
并已被逮捕
and has been arrested.
我很抱歉 这一点也不好笑
I'm sorry. It's not funny.
我看得出这对任何人来说都很有趣 但我除外
I can see how that's funny to anybody but me.
好吧 好吧 如果它没有消失 就忽略它吧
All right, well, if it doesn't go away, just ignore it.
你不要对你的个人家庭发表评论
You don't comment on your personal family.
你爱你的女儿 希望她能从错误中吸取教训
You love your daughter and hope she learns from her mistakes.
如果她被定罪了 我有什么...
If she's convicted, what are my...
我有什么选择？
what are my options?
你没有
You have none.
好吧 我收回那句话 你可以赦免她
Well, I take that back, you could pardon her
但那会是你政治生涯的正式结束 所以... ...
but that's officially the end of your political career, so...
我不必等到我的任期结束时
I don't have to wait until the end of my term
再赦免某人？
to pardon someone?
我强烈建议这么做
I would strongly advise it
但是不行 你有权力赦免
but no, you have the authority to pardon
减轻刑罚 给予宽大处理
to commute sentence, grant clemency
只要你愿意
whenever you want.
但是 一旦你打开潘多拉的盒子 它就不会关闭 所以..,
But once you open that Pandora's Box
它就不会关闭 所以...
it does not close, so...
下一个地雷？
Next land mine?
环保组织与...
Environmental groups relating to...
狼群
wolves.
不惜一切代价避免他们  是的
Avoid them at all costs.  Yeah.
水牛和狼是我两届任期的祸根
Buffalo and wolves were the bane of my two terms.
他们是氪石
They are kryptonite.
你需要远离它们 并拼命尝试
You need to stay away and try like hell
以避免采取立场
to avoid taking a position.
而且你需要找一个环境顾问
And you need to get an environmental advisor.
不是你的一个牧场主朋友 而是一个环保主义者
Not one of your rancher buddies, an environmentalist.
一个了解他们的思维方式的人
Someone who understands the way that they think
这样 他们可以向你解释他们到底在想什么
so they can explain to you what the hell it is they're thinking.
这是我对这份工作的最好建议
Here's my best advice about this job.
好的州长会发起行动
Good governors initiate action
而坏的州长则把所有时间都花在反应上
and bad governors spend all their time reacting.
除了机场 还有很多事情需要清理
There are plenty of things to clean up besides an airport.
你是我所知道的唯一一个
You're the only man I know who would actually pout
为自己参加的选举获胜而撅嘴的人
over winning the election that he entered.
我没有赌气
I'm not pouting.
也许是后悔 但...不是赌气
Skulking, maybe, but... not pouting.
你知道 这和那个牧场一样是你的遗产
You know, this is as much your legacy as that ranch.
你是个聪明的女人 林奈尔
You're a smart woman, Lynelle.
噢 你才知道？
Oh, you're just figuring that out?
享受你的午餐吧 约翰 这是我请的
Just enjoy your lunch, John. It's on me.
行为不检？
Disorderly conduct?
好样的
Way to go.
不客气
You're welcome.
现在我得在高速路上捡垃圾了
Now I gotta pick up trash on the highway
用我所有他妈的空闲时间
with all my fucking free time.
哪辆车是你的？
Which car is yours?
我不能带你回去 我得去找海伦娜
I can't take you back. I have to go to Helena.
哪一辆？ 我是认真的
Which one?  I'm serious.
那么 你想让我怎么回家 杰米？
Well, how do you want me to get home, Jamie?
嗯？要我在匝道上把裙子撩起来吗？
Huh? Want me to hike my skirt up on the on-ramp?
这也不是你第一次吧
I doubt it'd be the first time.
这他妈的是什么？
What the fuck is that?
什么是什么？
What's what?
婴儿座椅 这他妈是干什么的？
The baby seat. What the fuck is that for?
你有孩子吗？
You have a child?
你有一个孩子吗 杰米？
Do you have a child, Jamie?
一个男孩
A boy.
上帝给了你一个男孩？
God gave you a boy?
你把我的子宫挖出来...
You have my womb cut out of me...
而上帝给了你一个男孩？
and God gave you a boy?
去你妈的！
Fuck you!
贝丝？
Beth?
让我猜猜看 是那只
Let me guess, is it that brood mare
竞选经理母猪吗？
of a fucking campaign manager?
是的 我看出来了
Yes.  I saw her coming.
贝丝
Beth.
拜托 贝丝 贝丝 停 停 停！
Come on, Beth. Beth, stop, stop, stop!
把你带到那个诊所是我一生中最大的遗憾
Taking you to that clinic is the greatest regret of my life.
你在这个星球上45年来
Of all the awful shit that you have done
所做的所有糟糕的事情中
in your 45 years on this planet
杰米  你可真会说啊
Jamie, that is... that is really saying something.
什么...
What...
你给他取了什么名字？
What did you name him?
他是以我的名字命名的
He's named after me.
他当然是！
Of course he is!
这就是这个世界他妈的需要的东西
That's what the world fucking needs.
另一个该死的你
Another fucking you.
贝丝
Beth.
爸爸不知道这件事 没有人知道这件事
Dad doesn't know about this. Nobody knows about this.
别担心我会告诉他
Don't worry about me telling him.
我要把他从你身边夺走
I'm gonna take him from you.
我要剥夺你父亲的身份 杰米
I'm going to rob you of fatherhood, Jamie.
你不配拥有
You don't deserve it.
而他值得比你更好的
And he deserves better than you.
下一次你看到他 你可以吻他告别
Next time you see him, you can kiss him goodbye
因为他已经走了
because he's as good as gone.
汽车故障？
Car trouble?
事实上 我刚从监狱出来
Actually, I just got out of jail.
当他们让你出来时 他们只是让你出来
And when they let you out, they just let you out
没有 呃 没有给朋友打过电话
there's no, uh, no phone call to a friend
也没有汽车票
or a bus ticket.
只是 你知道 让你在街上走走
Just, you know, let you out on the street.
这似乎是对一个明显在社会上有困难的人
Seems an unfair policy toward one who is clearly
不公平的政策 你不觉得吗？
having trouble coping in society, don't you think?
肯定会产生 呃...
Definitely creates, uh...
额外的挑战是肯定的
Additional challenges for sure.
对吗？
Right?
你需要...  搭便车吗？
Do you need a...  Ride?
我很乐意
I'd love one.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你有香烟的几率是多少？
What are the odds that you have a cigarette?
不太好
Not good.
好吧 你可真可爱 不是吗？
Well, aren't you cute?
妈妈会杀了你的 爸爸
Mom's gonna kill you, Dad.
妈妈是吃醋的类型吗？
Is Mom the jealous type?
妈妈穿的是裤子 如果你知道我的意思
Mom wears the pants, if you know what I mean.
小妹妹 我完全明白你的意思
Sister, I know exactly what you mean.
把车停下来
Stop the car.
没有人告诉我
Nobody told me.
他没有告诉任何人
He didn't tell anybody.
只是停了下来 看到所有的车
Just pulled up and saw all the cars.
我们要不要 呃 靠近点？
Should we, uh, get closer?
我想这是他们希望我们靠近的地方 爸爸
I think this is as close as they want us, Dad.
那么 监狱怎么样？
So how was jail?
大声说话的娘们
Loud-mouthed pussy.
你和我一会儿要好好谈谈
You and I are going to have a long talk later.
是的 好吧 我待会儿要睡觉了
Yeah, well, I'm going to sleep later.
那我们现在就来个简短的吧
We'll have a short one now then.
控制冲动
Impulse control.
想点办法
Find some.
我认为他们不希望我们在这里
I don't think they want us here.
即使他们不想我们在这里
Even if they don't want us
他们也需要知道我们有足够的关心才会留下来
they need to know we care enough to stay.
给我一个承诺
Make me a promise.
永远不要让他们对我这样做
Don't ever let them do that to me.
把我变成灰烬 把我扔到风中
Turn me to ashes and throw me to the wind.
这就是我想要的所有关怀
That's all the care I want.
约翰
John.
我不清楚流程的内容
I'm not sure the protocol.
现在没有流程了
There's no protocol now.
仪式结束了
Ceremony's over.
我希望我早点知道
I wish I'd known.
悲伤不应该被分享
Grief isn't meant to be shared.
但安慰是可以的
But comfort is.
他们现可以需要些安慰
They could use some now.
约翰...
John...
这不是个好地方 但我们确实需要谈谈
This isn't the place but we do need to talk.
谈什么？
About what?
关于你在取消机场项目时
About the three hundred jobs you eliminated
消除的三百个工作岗位
when you canceled the airport project.
在保留地有很多非常不高兴的人
A lot of very unhappy people on the Reservation.
你明天能在国会大厦见我吗？
Can you meet me at the Capitol tomorrow?
我认为你应该在保留地见我
I think you should meet me on the Reservation.
向人们展示你对他们的关心和访问
Show the people you care enough to visit.
我可以做到这一点
I can do that.
我知道你的感受
I know how you feel.
我希望我不知道 但我知道
I wished I didn't, but I do.
我就在那里埋葬了一个儿子
I buried a son right over there.
我记得
I remember.
责备自己 是吗？
Blaming yourself, aren't you?
是的 我也这么做过
Yeah, I did that, too.
有些时候还是这样
Still do some days.
我告诉你一些我从来没有告诉过别人的事情
I'll tell you something I've never told anybody.
我有一个兄弟 大约18个小时
I had a brother for about eighteen hours.
他的名字叫彼得
His name was Peter.
他很早就出生了
He was born early
他的小心脏还不够强壮
and his little heart wasn't strong enough.
在那些日子里 他们能做的不多
Not much they could do back in those days.
现在他们也不能做很多事情
Not a lot they can do now.
所以 他们就把他还给了我母亲
So, they just gave him back to my mother.
医生们希望 我们祈祷 但...
The doctors hoped and we prayed and...
都没有成功
neither worked.
这改变了我母亲 这使她变得坚强
And it changed my mother. It hardened her.
她再也没有...她再也没有尝试生孩子
She never... she never tried to have children again.
多年后 我长大了 李刚刚出生的时候
Years later, I was grown and Lee had just been born.
我的父母都在看着他 轮流抱着他
Both my parents are looking at him, taking turns holding him.
而我的父亲脸色变得惨白 像个幽灵
And my father got white as a ghost
望着我母亲说
looked at my mother and said
"彼得活得很完美
"Peter lived a perfect life.
"他在这个星球上看到的只有你
"All he saw of this planet was you
他所知道的是你爱他 "
and all he knew was you loved him."
那个男孩过着完美的生活 莫妮卡
That boy lived a perfect life, Monica.
我们是唯一知道它是短暂的人
We're the only ones who know it was brief.
他只知道的是你和你爱他
All he knew was you and that you loved him.
谢谢你
Thank you.
用我的名字给他命名
Named him after me.
是的
I did.
这比你知道的更有意义 儿子
Means more than you'll ever know, son.
我知道这意味着什么
I know what it means.
是的
Yeah.
拿着这个
Hang on to this.
即使你不使用它
Even if you don't use it
现在也不是停止领取工资的时候
now is not the time to stop drawing a paycheck.
我会找人接替你的位置
I'll find someone to take your place
如果这是你想要的
if that's what you want.
这是我想要的
It's what I want.
你看起来累坏了
Looks like you got tossed off one.
只是一直在挖坟
Just been digging graves.
马一起葬了 你知道吗
Horses go in the field, you know that.
是的 我知道...但他们想把它放在那个男孩旁边
Yeah, I know but they wanted it beside the boy.
还以为你会不同意呢
Didn't figure you'd say no.
他们有说为什么吗？
They say why?
我猜是那孩子要有东西要骑去天堂
My guess is the boy has something to ride into Heaven.
呃 Poison Creek公司的人联系我们了
Uh, the Poison Creek outfit, they reached out
他们缺人做标记
they're short handed to brand.
他们需要我们的帮助 如果你同意的话
They wanted our help so, if you're all right with it
明天就去那里
go over there tomorrow.
我们什么时候开始？
When are we starting?
嗯 下周
Well, next week.
你打算在这里 不是吗？
You plan on being here, don't you?
我的意思是 这不是我的地方
I mean, it's not my place to
我会到的  好的
I'll be here.  All right.
公园巡警来问我
Park Rangers came and asked me
一些关于狼在这里聚集的问题
some question about wolves that held up here.
你知道这事吗？
You know anything about that?
嗯 他们捕食了一头牛
Mm. They pulled down a cow
我让瑞安出去射杀它们
and I asked Ryan to go out and shoot 'em.
他射杀了那些有该死项圈的狼
He shot the ones with the damn collars on 'em.
我担心这将给你带来麻烦
I was worried that it was going to cause you a problem
所以我想智取它们 但我想我没有做到
so I tried to outsmart 'em and I guess I didn't.
所以 我很抱歉 先生
So, I'm sorry, sir.
狼群现在在哪里？
Where are the wolves now?
在一个没人能找到它们的地方
In a place that nobody will ever find them.
马在天堂
Horses in heaven.
嗯 嗯 这是我能想到的最好的办法
Mm-hm. That's the best I could figure it.
那不是很好吗？
Wouldn't that be something?
♪ Well, in you ♪
♪ The good I'll do Good I'll do, oh ♪
♪ The good I'll do ♪
♪ The way the grass smells At night ♪
♪ And you've got flames All in your eyes ♪
♪ As they reflect the sparkler ♪
♪ And you say we'll never die ♪
♪ Grab me by the hands Just as callused as I am ♪
♪ Say your proud ♪
♪ Well, there's blue jeans in the driveway ♪
♪ And you're walking Inside sideways ♪
♪ The wine always affects you In beautiful kind ways ♪
♪ Ask me if I'm staying And I say that I'm ♪
♪ Sleeping on the floor ♪
♪ Won't you tell me that you need me ♪
♪ 'Cause lately I've been Needing someone to remind me ♪
♪ I'm worth more than Just an evening ♪
♪ I awoke to kitchen smoke, You dancin' ♪
♪ Like God's moved In you before ♪
♪ Well, in you ♪
♪ The good I'll do Good I'll do, oh ♪
♪ Good I'll do ♪
♪ Well, in you ♪
♪ I'm new, I'm new Oh, how I'm new ♪
♪ Look in my eyes ♪
♪ I don't wanna to hide ♪
♪ I've been waiting for you All damn night ♪
I know but he's gotta go somewhere.
♪ Sundress, I'll undress With nails on your skin ♪
♪ Turning white ♪
♪ Getting high out in Austin Drunk in Tennessee ♪
♪ I don't care where I am As long as you're with me ♪
♪ Those boys downtown talk So much shit when I leave ♪
干得好 里斯
Good job, Reese.
♪ Well, in you ♪
♪ The good I'll do Good I'll do, oh ♪
♪ The good I'll do ♪
♪ 'Cause in you ♪
♪ I'm new, I'm new Oh, how I'm new ♪
♪ The way the grass smells At night ♪
♪ And you've got flames All in your eyes ♪
♪ As they reflect the sparkler ♪  Whoo!
♪ And you say we'll never die ♪
♪ Grab me by the hands Just as callused as I am ♪
♪ Say your proud ♪
那么 今年你们有多少头牛？
So how many are y'all running this year?
和去年差不多
Bout the same as last year.
但我们今年不会增加任何小牛
But we won't add any yearlings this year though.
不能在这柴油和玉米价格上涨的时候
Not with diesel prices and corn.
是的 该死
No.  Shit.
当这东西最终被送到肉店的时候
When this finally makes it to the butcher shop
那就有苦吃了
it's gonna sting.
很高兴看到你儿子回来
It's good to see your boy back.
只是夏天而已
It's just for the summer.
他毕业了 在博伊西找到了一份工作
He graduated, got a job in Boise.
但我女儿想留下来
But my daughter wants to stay.
我们将看看我是否能把她
We'll see if I can make a cowboy out of her
脑子进水的丈夫变成一个牛仔
shit-for-brains husband.
他唯一喜欢做的事就是生孩子
Only thing he seems to like making is babies.
是这样吗？
Is that right?
你所在的世界确实在缩小
World sure is shrinking where you are.
很高兴看到机场项目被制止
It's good to see that airport squashed.
这不会改变什么 戴尔伯特
That ain't gonna change nothing, Delbert.
我的意思是 该死的 它可能会减慢一点
I mean, shit, it might slow it down a bit.
至少世界还没有发现这个地方
At least the world hasn't found out about this place yet.
想到我们留给他们的世界 我就心碎
It breaks my heart to think of the world we're leaving them.
我的心也碎了
Breaks my heart, too.
见鬼 我甚至没有任何孩子
Hell, I don't even have any kids.
希金斯
Higgins.
你怎么花了这么长时间？
What took you so long?
我才刚当上一个星期的州长
I've only been Governor a week.
看来你活下来了
I see you survived.
谢谢你  好吧 这其实有诈
Thank you.  Well, there's a catch.
有诈？
A catch?
是的 这是一个为期六个月的监督性释放
Yeah, it's a supervised release for six months.
由谁监督？
Supervised by who?
你面前的这个人
You're looking at him.
那么 你把我从监狱里放出来就是为了绑架我？
So, you release me from prison just to kidnap me?
或多或少 需要你的帮助
More or less. Need your help.
帮什么？
With what?
帮我了解你
Help me understand you.
帮助我了解你的思维方式
Help me understand the way you think.
我能得到什么回报？
What do I get in return?
你刚刚得到了它 进来吧
You just got it. Get in.
我待在哪里？ 和我一起
Where am I staying?  With me.
我不是政治战略家
I'm no political strategist
但给一个要在州长官邸与你同居的女人宽恕
but granting clemency to a woman you're shacking up with
本身就会引起一些负面新闻
in the Governor's mansion lends itself to some negative press.
在牧场
At the ranch.
噢 太好了 和你的躁郁狂反社会的女儿住一起？
Oh, great. With your bi-polar sociopathic daughter?
她几乎从不在那里
She's hardly ever there.
所以你知道 我刚刚经历了一年的无性生活
So you know, I just went a year without sex
这是我第一次做爱以来最长的一次
which is the longest I've gone since the first time I had it
但我也不会和你上床的
and I'm still not fucking you.
噢 上帝
Oh, God.
我们的关系将是纯粹的职业关系
Our relationship will be purely professional.
让她进来
Let her in.
阿特伍德小姐
Miss Atwood.
噢 来吧 是莎拉 请坐吧
Oh, come on. It's Sarah. Have a seat.
我冒昧地给我们点了一瓶玫瑰酒
I took the liberty of ordering us a bottle of Rosé.
我希望你不要介意
I hope you don't mind.
嗯 不能说我曾经喝过它
Well, can't say I've ever had it.
噢 嗯 法国人
Oh. Well the French
他们在夏天把它当水喝
they drink it like water in the summer.
试试吧
Try it.
它很清爽
It's refreshing.
这很好
It's nice.
什么？
What?
哦 我只是想决定
Oh, I'm just trying to decide
最好的前进道路
the best path forward.
我们如何处理这个问题？
How do we manage this?
我们作为一个公司 如何恢复？
How do we as a company, recover?
我们如何挽回面子？
How do we save face?
但最重要的是 我们如何扭转他的决定？
But most importantly, how do we reverse his decision?
要么推翻他的决定 要么把我们的钱拿回来
Either reverse his decision or get our money back.
我的意思是 国家正面临着数十亿美元的诉讼
I mean, the state is facing a multi-billion dollar lawsuit
你也知道
and you know it.
你不会赢的
You won't win.
随着一些最重要的元素
With some of the most vital elements
你的发展现在在保护地役权中
of your development now in a Conservation Easement
这个争论是没有意义的
the argument is moot.
我们不一定要赢
We don't have to win.
我们只需要让它在新闻中出现足够长的时间
We just need to keep it in the news long enough
来影响你父亲的名誉
to assassinate your father's reputation
并选择一个政治家来支持下一任州长
and choose a politician to support as the next governor.
嗯
Hm.
我已经说得很清楚了
I'm getting ahead of myself.
这次晚宴的目的是为了寻求软着陆
The purpose of this dinner was to seek a soft landing.
不是为了威胁立场
Not to threaten positions.
让我们先弄清楚我们是否能够相处得来
Let's figure out if we can even get along first.
你饿了吗？
Are you hungry?
不太饿
Not really.
嗯 我也不饿
Mm-mm. Me neither.
我已经吃够了这些水果味的东西
I've had enough of this fruity shit.
你想去酒吧吗？
Do you want to go to the bar?
当然
Sure.
哦 这不好笑
Oh, that's not funny.
那你为什么笑？
Then why are you laughing?
我笑是因为我很不舒服
I'm laughing because I'm uncomfortable.
你不舒服是因为你觉得好笑
You're uncomfortable because you find it funny.
我很害怕在法庭上和你争论
I'm dreading arguing with you in court.
你应该怕的
You should. You should.
是吗？
Yeah?
你怎么还单身呢？
How the hell are you still single?
嗯...
Well...
当你住在离镇子一小时的牧场上...
when you live on a ranch an hour from town...
一个小时的路程...
an hour from anything...
你现在不再是住在牧场上了
You don't live on a ranch anymore.
嗯 是的
Hm. No, I don't.
我觉得有点不负责任
I'm feeling a little irresponsible.
嗯
Hm.
我自己也开始有这种感觉了
I'm starting to feel that way myself, too.
哦
Oh.
带我去个地方证明一下吧
Take me somewhere and prove it.
♪ But you know I've always been ♪
跟着我
Follow me.
好的 我没有听到任何人
Okay. I don't hear anybody.
哇
Wow.
这边走
This way.
你...  不
You...  No.
这就是我所说的该死的浴室
This is what I call a fucking bathroom.
等等 等等...
Wait. Wait...
谁在乎呢？让他听
Who cares? Let him listen.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
没什么 宝贝 只是在思考
Nothing, baby. Just thinking.
也许你应该考虑一下不同的东西
Maybe you should think about something different.
我很想这样做 但是...这是不可能的
I'd love to. But... it ain't gonna happen.
回去睡觉吧
Go back to sleep.
这个婊子是谁？
Who is this bitch?
好吧 不是她的真名
Yeah, not her real name.
真让人吃惊
What a surprise.
我们的司法系统正处于彻底崩溃的状态 是吧？
Our Justice system is in a state of utter collapse, huh?
想想我为了把你送进监狱所做的一切努力
And to think of all the hard work I did to put you in prison.
再想想我为了不进监狱所做的一切努力
And think of all the hard work I'm doing to stay out.
我指的是努力
And I do mean hard.
等我进城里 我会给你买一些强力霉素
I'll pick you up some Doxycycline when I'm in town
杀死你在监狱里所感染上的任何病菌
to kill whatever funk your snatch caught in the clink.
谢谢 你能不能也给我买一个牙刷？
Mm. Thanks. Could you also get me a toothbrush?
我讨厌一直用你的
I hate to keep using yours.
哦 好吧 回去工作了
Oh, well. Back to work.
我可不想今天的开始是清醒的
I am not starting this day sober.
黄石下一集...
Next time on Yellowstone...
第一批定居在这个山谷的达顿家族...
First Duttons to settle this valley...
战斗是他们所知道的一切
fighting was all they knew.
她不会帮你的 爸爸
She is not gonna help you, Dad.
你已经邀请了你最大的敌人睡在你的床上
You have invited your worst enemy to sleep in your bed.
市场股票公司或其合作伙伴
Market Equities or its partners.
我们可以做任何我们想做的事
We can do whatever we want.
他们想要那块土地 爸爸
They want the land, Dad.
这就是你需要了解的一切
That is all that you need to understand.
这些天 懦夫统治着世界 里普
Cowards rule the world these days, Rip.
我想现在是时候让他们看看我们做什么和怎么做了
I think it's time we showed them what we do and how we do it.